One problem with subqueries is that they can
هناك مشكلة مع الاستعلامات الفرعية وهي أنها يمكن
make your queries lengthy and difficult to read.
أن تجعل استعلاماتك طويلة ويصعب قراءتها.
Common Table expressions or CTEs can help break
من الممكن أن تساعدك عبارات الجدول العامة أو CTEs
your query into separate components so that your query logic is more easily readable.
في تقسيم استعلامك إلى مكونات منفصلة حتى يكون منطق الاستعلام أكثر سهولة في القراءة.
You can read the subqueries logic on its
يمكنكم قراءة منطق الاستعلامات الفرعية بمفرده
own and then read the final queries logic easily as well.
ثم قراءة منطق الاستعلام النهائي بسهولة أيضًا.
Let's look back over this example in which we found the average number of events per
لنعود إلى هذا المثال الذي وجدنا فيه متوسط عدد الأحداث
day in each marketing channel.
يوميًا في كل قناة تسويق.
Let's break the subquery out into
لتقسم الاستعلام الفرعي إلى
his own common table expression which we'll create using the WITH command.
عبارات الجدول العامة التي سننشئها باستخدام أمر WITH.
Here, we're only defining
هنا، نحدد فقط
this one common table expression but we could theoretically write as many as we want.
عبارة الجدول العامة ولكن يمكننا نظريًا كتابة ما نريد.
We need to define any common table expressions at the beginning of
نحتاج إلى تحديد أي عبارات الجدول العامة الشائعة في بداية
the query in order to use them in our final query at the bottom.
الاستعلام لكي نستخدمها في الاستعلام النهائي في الأسفل.
Each common table expression gets an alias just like a subquery.
يُطلق على كل عبارة جدول عامة اسمًا مستعارًا مثل الاستعلام الفرعي.
Here, that alias is events.
هنا، هذا الاسم المستعار هو الأحداث.